I read some update like Multi Math Hi in the futures international market of
Vedantak in the morning, the business of rulers is also
in this, keep in mind that good moves are
visible, the deception of dead percent, while selling the bike at this time,
everything came on the radar on this stock, according to
me, a showing trading will be
good here, it is
trading above 400 at present, so
buy here with a stop loss of 395,
repeat the target that should be in front, Ashish ji, I said
Balrampur Chini, which is currently trading above 400,
so buy it is
close, just keep this in mind,
after buying Balrampur Chini Mill,
Sachin will do something,
today Ashish ji, we have given this recommendation to our
clients also, I am getting it,
here in ICC Lombard, a lot
of low pot sequence was going on, I have been getting it for about eight
weeks, that story is getting
arrested, a positive divergence was
visible on the daily chart.  Its effect
should be visible here and the way the
structure is, the way the open low has happened
this morning, I am thinking that it would be advisable to
add fresh longs here with a stoppage of 108. The
intraday target
will be around 1130 and the position target will be
around 11:55. I want to buy
in ICC Lombard futures.
OK Nifty 17520 Bank Nifty Nifty
IT's high was 3000050, it has
not been crossed yet, remember that fresh
advantage Nifty has just come, it is not
in the mood to give up, 3000050. Note down the level on Nifty Bank
and please convert your chats for a
little 5 minutes and see. The
Friday's near
90% trading and cluster of Nifty Bank was 1740
654,
remember this, its level will emerge but
whose is 3050, so remember that
I have an advantage for the index. Ashish's
view  It is being said that Reliance is
in a good mood today after both the days. Look,
Reliance is picking up 239 on your screen. It has already crossed the
Hi Special of yesterday's session i.e. Friday from the lower level.
Kavita ji, what will be your tweet.
Currently there is a resistance. One should cross it
for the target of 292. Birla Software should
initiate a white red. One can take the
stock plus of 299 on the position of
small company IT or big company.
Birla Soft Kavita ji's Preferred
Cap IT is on your screen. Chandan, today's
quick single is to run.
Comparatively, oil, gas, power or selective
capital goods are held in this market, then
focus will be kept there only.
Buying advice will be given. There is support of 1504 in the counter. On the
upside, there should be a swing till about 161-162.